

ALICIA MORALES

COMPUTER SCIENCE FNGINFFR

ADDRESS:

Hospitalet de Llobregat 08904



PHONE:

+34 665 37 07 08



EMAIL:

alicia5324@gmail.com



SKYPE:

alice2360



DATE OF BIRTH:

24 February 1995



WEBSITE:

aliciamorales.ml

SKILLS

JAVA

SCALA

PYTHON

C

SOCIAL



github.com/amoralca16



twitter.com/amoralca16



linkedin.com/in/aliciamorales-carrasco-81a3ba8

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

good English oral and writen communication skills.

Graduate of Computer Science Engineering at Universitat de Barcelona with in-depth knowledge in programming and a great interest in Big Data and Artificial Intelligence. Comprehensive knowledge on database software, experience with Agile methodologies and

"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." - Thomas A. Edison

ACHIEVEMENTS

Universitat de Barcelona

MACHINE LEARNING Completed a course on Statistical and Machine Learning where I could learn and practise the fundamentals of ML and Deep Learning with R.

GAME DEVELOPER

2016-2017

Made two game development projects with Unity and C#, one with a team of twenty people and another one in a hackathon. Both were the winners of their respective contests.

WEB DEVELOPER

2016-2017

Created a flight purchasing site using RESTful, Django and Javascript.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

2013-2018

2011-2013

Universitat de Barcelona

Specialized on Distributed Artificial Intelligence, Distributed Software, Machine Learning and Data Mining. Mark: 8.03

TECH BATXILLERAT Graduated with honors, PAU June 2013. Mark: 9.01

INS Vicenc Plantada

WORK EXPERIENCE

BIG DATA ENGINEER

10.2018 - Present SCRM Lidl Digital

- Modeled data sources

- Did Spark Scala ETLs
- Designed Databricks metastore
- Supported Business Intelligence non-normalized layer
- Orchestrated Spark jobs, integrated CI/CD pipelines and more.

COMPUTER VISION

02.2018 - 06.2018 colorSensing

Developed an image processing and computer vision software for the quantitative analysis of test strips.

Designed and developed the Lidl international analytics data platform.

BIG DATA INTERN

10.2017 - 01.2018 Everis Spain, S.L.U. Supported the development of Big Data projects doing testing, preparing documentation and suggesting improvements. Worked with Big Data Architecture: Spark, Hadoop, Scala, AWS, Azure...

2017 - 2018

Universitat de Barcelona

PROFESSOR ASSISTANT Lectured, designed assignments and helped in programming and data structures subjects.